http://www.crystalgraphics.com/privacy.asp

CrystalGraphics
Toggle navigation
PowerPlugs Ultimate ComboTemplates for PowerPointPowerPictures PhotosCharts & Diagrams3D Character SlidesVideo BackgroundsMore Products
CrystalGraphics Privacy Policy
Welcome to CrystalGraphics' Internet website!
We are proud to have this opportunity to tell you a little about our products
and our company. We are confident you like what you see. But before you
begin exploring, we'd like to review the steps we have taken to ensure
that on-line visitors of all ages have a safe, enjoyable experience.
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. At CrystalGraphics,
we value our customers’ privacy and have made it our policy to provide
on-line content that requires minimal collection of information from our
visitors. Furthermore, to better protect your privacy we provide this
notice explaining our on-line information practices and the choices you
can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make
this notice easy to find, we intend to make it available on our homepage
and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Any significant changes to this Privacy Policy shall be printed in blue
italics for a period of 30 days.
How We Collect Information
Below are some of the ways in which a visitor
may provide information to us on-line and how we may use that information.
Domain Name Recognition
Our web servers automatically recognizes
a visitor's domain name, however, they do not recognize a visitor's e-mail.
Use of Cookies
Cookies are small bits of information that
a website transfers to an individual's computer for record keeping purposes.
We use cookies in a variety of ways to create a more personalized on-line
experience for the user. These cookies contain no personal information
about you and no one but CrystalGraphics can retrieve the cookies. These
cookies are stored within your browser. Information which may be obtained
through cookies is not sold, rented or provided to third parties and is
not used internally by CrystalGraphics for any purpose other than to learn
in the aggregate which websites may have referred our website visitors,
as well as to enhance your experience on our website.
Information Actively Provided by
Our Visitors
We do not require visitors to register or
provide any information before entering our websites. However, there are
several places where visitors may choose to provide personally identifiable
information about themselves. CrystalGraphics treats this information
as strictly confidential. Unless we tell you otherwise, CrystalGraphics
uses the information only for the purpose it was provided and will not
give, lease, trade, share or sell this personal information to another
entity or person outside of CrystalGraphics.
For example:
E-Newsletters: Some
of our pages permit you to register to receive e-mail newsletters and/or
product or promotional update emails in the future by providing your
name and e-mail address. We will not give, lease, trade, share or sell
these names or email addresses to another entity or person outside of
CrystalGraphics. Any e-mail you receive from CrystalGraphics will allow
you to "unsubscribe" from this informational service at any
time.
Free or Trial Product Downloads:
Some of our pages permit you to download free or trial software
after providing your name and e-mail address. Generally, just below
those name and email fields, you are also provided with an option to
receive e-mail newsletters and/or product or promotional update emails
in the future. We will not give, lease, trade, share or sell these names
or email addresses to another entity or person outside of CrystalGraphics.
Any e-mail you receive from CrystalGraphics will allow you to unsubscribe
from this informational service at any time.
Purchase Pages: You
may also buy products on our website, in which case you will be asked
for your name, address and credit card or other payment information.
This information will be treated by CrystalGraphics as strictly confidential
and is used by CrystalGraphics only for the purpose of verifying and
collecting the payment and shipping the order to you at the address
specified. It is never provided in any form to any person outside CrystalGraphics
or to any other company, except that your name and address are provided
to our shipping company and, in some cases, to the government for tax
purposes, if required by law. Any follow-up or product or promotional
e-mail you receive from CrystalGraphics after your purchase will allow
you to unsubscribe from this informational service at any time.
Questions: On some pages
our visitors can submit comments or ask questions. The only personally
identifiable information that we collect is the sender’s name
and e-mail address. We will not give, lease, trade, share or sell these
names or email addresses to another entity or person outside of CrystalGraphics.
We do not save any personally identifiable information associated with
comments, and we only save e-mail addresses associated with questions
in order to respond to those questions.
Sweepstakes: We occasionally
offer sweepstakes on our pages. We collect the name and email addresses
of the people entering the sweepstakes. Rarely, this information may
be shared with the company providing the sweepstakes prizes, but if
so, this fact will be clearly stated in the online entry form. Otherwise,
we will not give, lease, trade, share or sell these names or email addresses
to another entity or person outside of CrystalGraphics. Of course, we
also collect the information necessary for prize fulfillment from those
who win. If a prize is valued at over $600, a social security number
will be requested. The first initial, last name, hometown and state
of all winners will be included on a Winners List. The Winners List
will be provided upon request and as required by law. Information required
for tax purposes, email addresses, the Winner’s List or other
information required by law is kept as required by law. All other information
is deleted within 60 days of the final selection of the sweepstakes’
prize winners.
Other Features: There
may be other features available on our website which may require some
personally identifiable information to use the feature. We only use
the personally identifiable information to provide the feature and delete
it within a reasonable period of time after the information is no longer
necessary.
Unsubscribing from Our Email List
Every promotional
e-mail you receive from CrystalGraphics should offer you the means to
easily unsubscribe from CrystalGraphics’ mailing list within 72
hours. If you have difficulties using this feature, or want to report
any problems with its effectiveness, you may report any such problems
and/or request that you be immediately unsubscribed by contacting
us. If you want to find out how and when you got on our mailing list,
you may also contact us at this same email address.
Aggregate Information
Aggregate information about which pages
visitors visit is only used for internal review as we continue to improve
our website.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain
data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put
in place appropriate and effective physical, electronic, and managerial
procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on-line.
This Privacy Policy Is For Our On-line
Customers and Website Visitors
This Privacy Policy is for our customers
and others who visit our website. It does not apply to information which
we may collect by means other than over the Internet.
Links
Our policy is to occasionally provide electronic
links to other sites which may be of interest to visitors to our website.
However, content on websites can change quickly, so we cannot always guarantee
the appropriateness of the content of sites we link to.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns
about our privacy policy, please don't hesitate to contact us.
See the Contact Us link in the Help section below.
CrystalGraphics, Inc.
1999 S. Bascom Avenue
Suite 700
Campbell, CA USA 950008
Your Friends at CrystalGraphics
Copyright © CrystalGraphics, Inc.
Effective:
January 20, 2004
93%
of Fortune 1000 companies use our PowerPoint Products
Standing Ovation AwardWinner: Best PowerPointTemplate Collection
Network Solutions protects your online transactions with secure SSL encryption.
200,000+ satisfied customers worldwide!
100% satisfaction guatantee - or send it back for a refund!
Sign up for our free newsletter! You'll get news about our PowerPoint-enhancing product line – including free updates, new product announcements and exclusive special offers.
Plus you'll get a link to a free PowerPoint template with every newsletter you receive.
CrystalGraphics, Inc. 1999 S. Bascom Avenue Suite 700 Campbell, CA 95008 USA
© 2020 CrystalGraphics, Inc. All rights Reserved.
|
PowerPlugs is a trademark of CrystalGraphics, Inc.
Microsoft and the PowerPoint logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries.
+
